<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hallucinogenic on Ayaselva</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hallucinogenic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hallucinogenic on Ayaselva</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hallucinogenic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ayahuasca center of psychedelic healing journeys..</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/blog001-ayahuasca-center-of-psychedelic-healing-journeys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/blog001-ayahuasca-center-of-psychedelic-healing-journeys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ayahuasca, a traditional brew from South America, is known for its powerful hallucinogenic properties and has been used for centuries in spiritual and healing rituals by indigenous tribes. In recent years, its use has spread to North America and Europe, attracting people in their 20s and 30s who travel to countries like Brazil and Peru, particularly Iquitos, to participate in ayahuasca ceremonies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When consumed, ayahuasca induces hallucinations and spiritual experiences, which are believed to stem from increased introspection. The effects start about 30 minutes after ingestion and can last up to 8 hours. The brew typically contains the Banisteriopsis caapi vine, which has monoamine oxidase A (MAO-A)-inhibiting beta-carbolines, and is often mixed with leaves from the Chacruna or Chagropanga plants, which are rich in the psychedelic compound DMT. Without the MAO-A inhibitor, DMT would be broken down by the body and remain inactive. However, when combined, these ingredients allow DMT to be absorbed and cross the blood-brain barrier, leading to profound psychological and physical effects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
